Sky Striker vs.
Kewl Tune.
Game 1.
Kewl Tune goes first.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Cue, then Special Summons Kewl Tune Rotary.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Track Maker.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Rotary, then chains Kewl Tune Cue in response, then chains Kewl
Tune Track Maker in response.
Kewl Tune adds Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck, then banishes Forbidden Crown from the Deck,
then adds Kewl Tune Synchro from the Deck.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Synchro, then adds Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Loudness War.
Kewl Tune activates JJ "Kewl Tune".
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Mix.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Mix, then adds Kewl Tune Cue from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Remix.
Kewl Tune activates JJ "Kewl Tune", then sends Kewl Tune Remix to the Graveyard, then adds
Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck.
Sky Striker draws Ghost Belle & Haunted Mansion.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
, then chains Sky Striker Mobilize - Linkage!
in response, then Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari.
Sky Striker adds Sky Striker Ace - Raye from the Deck.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Kagari, then recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Hayate using Sky Striker Ace - Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Special Maneuver - Lemnisgate!
, then returns Sky Striker Ace - Kagari to the Extra Deck, then returns Sky Striker
Mobilize - Linkage!
to the Deck.
Sky Striker's Sky Striker Ace - Hayate attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Hayate, then sends Sky Striker Mecha - Shark Cannon
from the Deck to the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Shizuku using Sky Striker Ace - Raye as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Special Maneuver - Lemnisgate!
, then banishes Sky Striker Special Maneuver - Lemnisgate!.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace = Zero using Sky Striker Ace - Shizuku and
Sky Striker Ace - Hayate as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace = Zero.
Kewl Tune chains Ghost Ogre & Snow Rabbit in response to destroy Sky Striker Ace = Zero.
Sky Striker adds Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Deck.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Raye, then Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Raye, then Special Summons Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
, then adds Sky Striker Ace - Raye from the Deck.
, then adds Sky Striker Mobilize - Linkage!
from the Deck.
Sky Striker sets Forbidden Crown, then sets Sky Striker Mobilize - Linkage!.
Kewl Tune draws Kewl Tune Clip.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Mix.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Mix.
Sky Striker activates Forbidden Crown on Kewl Tune Mix, negating it and making it unable to
attack, be destroyed, be Tributed, or be used as Summon material this turn; it is also
unaffected by other activated effects.
Kewl Tune Mix's effect is negated.
Kewl Tune activates JJ "Kewl Tune", then sends Kewl Tune Loudness War to the Graveyard, then
adds Kewl Tune Cue from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Cue.
Sky Striker chains Ghost Belle & Haunted Mansion in response.
Kewl Tune Cue's effect is negated.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Crackle.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Cue, then chains Kewl Tune Crackle in response, then banishes Super
Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis.
Kewl Tune banishes Ghost Mourner & Moonlit Chill from the Deck.
Sky Striker returns Super Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis to the Extra Deck.
Sky Striker draws Sky Striker Mecha - Widow Anchor.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Linkage!
, then chains Sky Striker Mecha - Widow Anchor in response, then takes control of Kewl Tune Crackle.
Sky Striker Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Kagari, then recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker changes Kewl Tune Crackle from face-up Defense Position to face-up Attack Position, then Normal
Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace = Zero using Sky Striker Ace - Raye and
Sky Striker Ace - Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace = Zero, then recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker's Kewl Tune Crackle attacks Kewl Tune Mix, destroys it, and deals 700 damage.
Sky Striker's Sky Striker Ace = Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Kewl Tune regains control of Kewl Tune Crackle.
Kewl Tune draws Mulcharmy Purulia.
Kewl Tune activates JJ "Kewl Tune", then sends Kewl Tune Crackle to the Graveyard, then adds
Kewl Tune Reco from the Deck.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Crackle, then Special Summons Kewl Tune Crackle, then banishes Albion the Branded Dragon.
Kewl Tune banishes Super Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Reco.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Reco, then recovers Kewl Tune Rotary from the Graveyard.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Rotary.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Rotary.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Track Maker.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Rotary, then chains Kewl Tune Track Maker in response, then adds
Kewl Tune Reco from the Deck.
Kewl Tune returns Ghost Belle & Haunted Mansion to the Deck.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Reco.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Zalen the Shackled Dragon.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Track Maker, then returns Sky Striker Ace = Zero to the Extra Deck.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Raye, then Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Kewl Tune's Zalen the Shackled Dragon attacks and destroys Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker returns Super Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis to the Extra Deck, then returns Albion
the Branded Dragon to the Extra Deck.
Sky Striker draws The Fallen & The Virtuous.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
, then adds Sky Striker Ace - Raye from the Deck, then draws Sky Striker Ace - Roze.
, then adds Sky Striker Mobilize - Linkage!
from the Deck, then draws Sky Striker Mecha - Widow Anchor.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mecha - Widow Anchor, then chains Sky Striker Mobilize - Linkage!
in response, then Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari.
Sky Striker takes control of Zalen the Shackled Dragon.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Kagari, then chains Sky Striker Ace - Roze in
response, then Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Roze.
Sky Striker recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace = Zero using Sky Striker Ace - Roze and
Sky Striker Ace - Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace = Zero, then recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker activates The Fallen & The Virtuous, then sends Albion the Branded Dragon from the
Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Kewl Tune Crackle.
Sky Striker's Zalen the Shackled Dragon attacks directly for 2800 damage.
Sky Striker's Sky Striker Ace = Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Sky Striker wins the duel.
Sky Striker wins Game 1.
Sky Striker vs.
Kewl Tune.
Game 2.
Kewl Tune goes first.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Cue, then Special Summons Kewl Tune Rotary.
Kewl Tune activates Synchro Overtake, then Special Summons Kewl Tune Reco.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Reco, then adds Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Track Maker.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Rotary, then chains Kewl Tune Track Maker in response, then adds
Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck.
Kewl Tune adds Kewl Tune Synchro from the Deck.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Synchro, then adds Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune RS.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Loudness War.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Remix.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Cue, then banishes Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune B2B.
Sky Striker draws The Fallen & The Virtuous.
Kewl Tune activates Maxx "C".
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!.
Kewl Tune chains Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring in response to negate Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
's Deck effect.
Sky Striker chains Radiant Typhoon Chant in response, then adds Radiant Typhoon Swen from the Deck,
then Mobilize - Engage!
's effect is negated.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Raye, then Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari.
Kewl Tune draws Infinite Impermanence.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Kagari, then recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
, then adds Sky Striker Ace - Raye from the Deck.
Sky Striker activates The Fallen & The Virtuous, then sends Albion the Branded Dragon from the
Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Kewl Tune Loudness War.
Sky Striker activates Forbidden Droplet, then sends Radiant Typhoon Swen from the hand to the Graveyard,
then selects Kewl Tune B2B with Forbidden Droplet, negating its effects and halving its ATK until
the end of the turn.
Sky Striker's Sky Striker Ace - Kagari attacks Kewl Tune B2B, destroys it, and deals 300 damage.
Sky Striker activates Albion the Branded Dragon, then adds The Fallen & The Virtuous from the Deck.
Kewl Tune draws Dominus Purge.
Kewl Tune sets Infinite Impermanence, then sets Dominus Purge.
Sky Striker draws Radiant Typhoon Vision.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Hayate using Sky Striker Ace - Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Radiant Typhoon Vision.
Kewl Tune chains Dominus Purge in response.
Radiant Vision's effect is negated.
Sky Striker's Sky Striker Ace - Hayate attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Hayate, then sends Sky Striker Mecha - Shark Cannon
from the Deck to the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari using Sky Striker Ace - Hayate as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Kagari.
Kewl Tune chains Infinite Impermanence in response.
Sky Striker Ace - Kagari's effect is negated.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Shizuku using Sky Striker Ace - Kagari as material.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace = Zero using Sky Striker Ace - Raye and
Sky Striker Ace - Shizuku as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace = Zero, then recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
, then adds Sky Striker Ace - Raye from the Deck, then draws Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring.
Sky Striker sets The Fallen & The Virtuous.
Kewl Tune draws Kewl Tune Cue.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Kewl Tune Cue.
Sky Striker chains Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring in response to negate Kewl Tune Cue's Deck effect.
Kewl Tune Cue's effect is negated.
Sky Striker activates The Fallen & The Virtuous, then sends Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon from
the Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Kewl Tune Cue.
Sky Striker draws Triple Tactics Talent.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari using Sky Striker Ace - Raye as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Ace - Kagari, then recovers Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!
from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Link Summons Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu using Sky Striker Ace - Kagari as material.
Sky Striker's Sky Striker Ace = Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Sky Striker's Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Kewl Tune draws Ghost Ogre & Snow Rabbit.
Sky Striker draws Radiant Typhoon Chant.
Sky Striker's Sky Striker Ace = Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Sky Striker's Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Sky Striker wins the duel.
Sky Striker wins Game 2.
Final score: Sky Striker 2–0.